4gltesolution.com 2012-09-15

# Privacy Policy

4G LTE Solution understands and appreciates that you are concerned about your privacy and about the confidentiality and security of information we may gain about you online and off-line. 4G LTE Solution is committed to protecting your privacy. 4G LTE Solution and its staff will adhere to the Commonwealth Privacy Act 2010 including the recently enacted National Privacy Principles.This Privacy Policy explains how your personal information will be treated as you access and interact with 4G LTE Solution

**Data Collection**

We will only collect information about you if it is pertinent to the type of request made. Information collection from you will typically be in the following circumstances:

If you have contacted us either by mail, telephone or via facsimile in relation to a product enquiry, customer service enquiry or response to a promotion, we will typically collect the following information: name, contact details, telephone, fax and e-mail details, as well as the details of your request. High level information in relation to your business may also be collected. The primary purpose of collecting this information is to enable us to provide you with better customer service.

**Use and Disclosure**

4G LTE Solution is the sole owner of the information collected. With the exception of information shared with our software business partners we will not provide any personally identifiable information whatsoever to third parties without your prior consent.

**Data Security and Storage**

4G LTE Solution takes reasonable steps to preserve the security of personal information both online and off-line.

While we use firewalls and access controls to protect information online, we also protect user information off-line. All of our users' information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need access to the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed as totally secure. 4G LTE Solution strives to protect such information, however we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

**Links to Other Web Sites**

The 4G LTE Solution web site may contain links to other web sites. Please be aware that 4G LTE Solution is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy policies of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by 4G LTE Solution

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this web site or at:

**Email** : sales@4gltesolution.com

**Tel**  : 852 69499341 Fax : 852 24201212

**Address** : 2F, Dah Sing Bldg,99-105 Des Voeux Rd, C, Central, Hongkong
